Marcel-André Hille

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Personal Profile

Software engineer with proven full-stack hands-on experience in web development, interactive application development and design thinking.

Skills

Design thinking Agile Project Management Software Architecture, OOP & Clean Code React.js & Redux, Vue.js, Angular.js, Node.js, SQL, NoSQL, Git, C#, Unity3D

Contact Details



0

+49 (0) 152 275 98 436 maredesign.founder@gmail.com https://github.com/GERInFact

> Johannesstraße 31A 70176 Stuttgart Germany

Experience

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

EDER GMBH (2019 - PRESENT)

Design, implement & maintain complex web-based applications Direct agile project management methodology Integrate & maintain database solutions

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

COBRA - COMPUTER'S BRAINWARE GMBH (2018)

Maintain & test CRM desktop application

DIRECTOR OF STUDIES

SAE INSTITUTE GMBH (2016 - 2018)

Direct BSc (Hons.) Games Programming Course Evolve public & business relations

LECTURER OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

SAE INSTITUTE GMBH (2016 - present)

Software Architecture, Design Patterns, UX, Game Mathematics, Game AI

Education

WEB DEVELOPMENT & DESIGN

CAREERFOUNDRY (2019 - 2020)

Full-Stack Development & Collaboration

BSC (HONS) GAMES PROGRAMMING, FIRST CLASS

SAE INSTITUTE GMBH (2014 - 2019)

- Academic Excellence Award
- ECTS Grade A

ISA SURF INSTRUCTOR LVL 1

SURFING AUSTRALIA (2013)

Other Projects:

- www.alber-pfindel.de, using HTML5, CSS3, ES6+
- Procedural Content Generator, using Unity3D
- BitBoard Game, using Bit Operations in Unity3D
- Interactive AR Truck Application Demo for Daimler, using Wikitude & Unity3D
- Game Al driven Android Hack n' Slay Game, using Unity3D
- Ticket management system, using DevExpess & SQL Server
- Database Migrator & Normalizer, using WinForms & SQL
- Games Immersion A Coding Camp for Gamer, founded in 2017